KELVIN LAU

Web Developer

DETAILS

ADDRESS

7 Tobago Drive, Milton Keynes Milton Keynes, MK3 5FT United Kingdom

PHONE

+44 7878397841

EMAIL

kelllvinuk@gmail.com

LINKS

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kelllvinl/

SKILLS

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

TypeScript

React

React Native

Node.js

Python

Git

PostgreSQL

Amazon AWS

Microsoft Office

PROFILE

A Hong Konger Just move to UK since Feb 2022 via BNO VISA. Have right to work and right to live. Currently working in Paradox studios as a Website Developer.

Before I move to the UK, I completed the Diploma in AI and Programming at Tecky Academy and which is a Level 5 Endorsed Course by TQUK.

After I quit my accounting job and start as a Freelance Web Developer. My latest project was a membership & event management system for a Hong Kong Non-Governmental Organization - The Hong Kong Federation of Youth Groups. It requires using React and React Native to complete. It has been deployed as a web page, and also there is an application for IOS and Android. I am capable to complete on front-end and back end.

As a Website Developer, I response

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

React Website Developer, Paradox Studios Northampton, UK Sep 2022

Creating and maintaining apps and web in frontend and backend

Freelance Web Developer

Hong Kong

Sep 2021 — Sep 2022

- To help customer to create and design a website and mobile
- Problem solving and maintenance on the website and mobile application.
- · Handle back-end data issue
- · Deploy the website and mobile app.

Billing Officer & Credit Consultant, Telstra International Limited

Hong Kong

Jun 2016 — Sep 2021

- · Issuing Invoice, Debit note & Credit note
- · Follow up billing equines, resolving dispute for customer
- · Handle AR and AP daily operation, monthly AR reporting
- · Assists on credit check on new customer

Customer Care Representative & Credit Control Officer, Pure International (HK) Limited

Hong Kong

Hong Kong

Jul 2012 — Jun 2016

- \cdot Responsible for timely cash collection and minimizing bad debts
- · Collect and follow up on all outstanding receivable
- · Monitor and check on overdue accounts receivables
- Greet guests, answer incoming calls and clarify customers' inquiries in a professional manner
- · Handle reservation and provide check-in and out services

Financial Consultant, Prudential Hong Kong Limited

Oct 2009 — Oct 2011

- · Financial analysis & planning services for clients' need
- providing investment in fund, target saving planning, various insurance planning

EDUCATION

Diploma in AI and Programming, Tecky Academy (endorsed by TQUK)

Hong Kong

Nov 2021 — Jan 2022

The MicroMaster in A.I. & Programming consist of a 16 week of full-time class. The course is focus on HTML/CSS/JS Track, JavaScript fundamentals, Web fundamentals in JS, Web server programming, Backend & Al development & Frontend development.

Tech Stack: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Reactnative, Python, SQL, Git

Bachelor of Arts in Business Administration, Saint Martin's University

United States

Sep 2006 — Aug 2009

Diploma in Hotel and Tourism Management, Hong Kong Institute of Hotel Management

Hong Kong

Sep 2004 — Apr 2006

High School Diploma, Niagara Christian College

Canada

Sep 2001 — Jun 2004

REFERENCES

References available upon request